[
    {
        "question": " ",
        "optionA": " ",
        "optionB": " ",
        "optionC": " ",
        "optionD": " ",
        "answer": " "
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
       "optionA": "Dog",
       "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
       "optionD": "Lion",
       "answer": "Elephant"
   },
   {
        "question": "Which state produces maximum soybean?",
        "optionA": "Madhya Pradesh",
        "optionB": "Uttar Pradesh",
        "optionC": "Bihar",
        "optionD": "Rajasthan",
        "answer": "Madhya Pradesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country operationalized world’s largest radio telescope?",
        "optionA": "USA",
        "optionB": "China",
        "optionC": "Russia",
        "optionD": "India",
        "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the capital of Arunachal Pradesh?",
        "optionA": "Itanagar",
        "optionB": "Dispur",
        "optionC": "Imphal",
        "optionD": "Panaji",
        "answer": "Itanagar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one among the following radiations carries maximum energy?",
        "optionA": "Ultraviolet rays",
        "optionB": "Gamma rays",
        "optionC": "X- rays",
        "optionD": "Infra-red rays",
        "answer": "Gamma rays"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following states is not located in the North?",
        "optionA": "Jharkhand",
        "optionB": "Jammu and Kashmir",
        "optionC": "Himachal Pradesh",
        "optionD": "Haryana",
        "answer": "Jharkhand"
    },
    {
        "question": "India’s first satellite of 2020 GSAT-30 was successfully launched is a",
        "optionA": "Remote Sensing Satellite",
        "optionB": "Communication Satelite",
        "optionC": "Spy Satellite",
        "optionD": "Metrological Satellite",
        "answer": "Communication Satelite"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which state is the main language Khasi?",
        "optionA": "Mizoram",
        "optionB": "Nagaland",
        "optionC": "Meghalaya",
        "optionD": "Tripura",
        "answer": "Meghalaya"
    },
    {
        "question": "The head quarters of world trade organization is in",
        "optionA": "Montreal",
        "optionB": "Seattle",
        "optionC": "Geneva",
        "optionD": "Hague",
        "answer": "Geneva"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest coffee producing state of India?",
        "optionA": "Kerala",
        "optionB": "Tamil Nadu",
        "optionC": "Karnataka",
        "optionD": "Arunachal Pradesh",
        "answer": "Karnataka"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the only mammal that can’t jump?",
        "optionA": "Dog",
        "optionB": "Elephant",
        "optionC": "Goat",
        "optionD": "Lion",
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "question": "The 2014 football world cup is scheduled to be held in",
        "optionA": "China",
        "optionB": "Australia",
        "optionC": "Japan",
        "optionD": "Brazil",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state has the largest population?",
        "optionA": "Uttar Pradesh",
        "optionB": "Maharastra",
        "optionC": "Bihar",
        "optionD": "Andra Pradesh",
        "answer": "Uttar Pradesh"
    },
    {
        "question": "The language spoken by the people by Pakistan is ?",
        "optionA": "Hindi",
        "optionB": "Palauan",
        "optionC": "Sindhi",
        "optionD": "Nauruan",
        "answer": "Sindhi"
    },
    {
        "question": "The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is",
        "optionA": "Silver",
        "optionB": "Zinc",
        "optionC": "Copper",
        "optionD": "Gold",
        "answer": "Silver"
    }
]